Guide to the New-York Historical Society Bequests, Gifts & Related Matters Record Group 1852-1992 NYHS-RG 16
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Bequests to Circa 1960, 1852-1986; 5.42 Linear feet in 13 document boxes
  - Woodman, Nora D., 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Bequest of studies from nature in oil, oil portraits, and engravings executed by Woodman's late grandfather, Asher B. Durand, and a financial legacy.
  - Wright, Kate L. Davis, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Zabriskie, George A., 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Financial legacy. Gift from estate of bookbinder's tools for use in N-YHS's bindery.